{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520941845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520941845"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520943910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520943910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520945976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520945976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520949098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520949098"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520951270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520951270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520953471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520953471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520956251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520956251"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520958414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520958414"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520960592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520960592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520963752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520963752"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520965803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520965803"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520967849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520967848"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520970848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520970847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520973082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520973082"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520975253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520975252"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520978168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520978168"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520980442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520980442"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520982735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520982735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520985705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520985705"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520987757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520987757"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520989840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520989840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520992878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520992878"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520994999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520994999"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548520997119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548520997118"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521000196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521000196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521002539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521002539"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521004896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521004896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521005128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521005128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521005210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521005210"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_194206"," gameId":" c5020a9b-f70e-4521-9453-9bd542df2dd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}